export const questions = [
    {
        prompt: "Who was called 'the servant of the Lord'?",
        answer: "Moses (Jos. 1:1)",
    },
    {
        prompt: "Whom did the Lord appoint to succeed Moses after his death?",
        answer: "Joshua (Jos. 1:1)",
    },
    {
        prompt: "Who was the father of Joshua?" ,
        answer: "Nun (Jos. 1:1)"
    },
    {
        prompt: "Who told Joshua to arise and go over the Jordan river?",
        answer: "The Lord (Jos. 1:2) "
    },
    {
        prompt: "What gift did the children of Israel receive from the Lord?",
        answer: "The land (Jos. 1:2)"
    },
    {
        prompt: "Fill in the blanks:\n'Every place that the _____ of your _____ will tread upon I have given you, as I said to Moses.'",
        answer: "Sole, foot (Jos. 1:6)",
    },
    {
        prompt: "What river was the Great River? ",
        answer: "The River Euphrates (Jos. 1:4)",
    },
    {
        prompt: "How long did God say no man would be able to stand before Joshua?",
        answer: "All the days of Joshua’s life (Jos. 1:5)",
    },
    {
        prompt: "The Lord would be with Joshua as he had been with whom?",
        answer: "Moses (Jos. 1:5)",
    },
    {
        prompt: "The land the Israelites received as an inheritance had been promised to whom?",
        answer: "To their fathers (Jos. 1:6)",
    },
    {
        prompt: "What two things does the Lord command Joshua to be?",
        answer: "Strong and courageous (Jos. 1:7)",
    },
    {
        prompt: "Why was Joshua not to turn from the law to the left or to the right?",
        answer: "To prosper wherever he goes (Jos. 1:7)",
    },
    {
        prompt: "What was Joshua told to meditate on day and night?",
        answer: "Book of the law (Jos. 1:8)",
    },
    {
        prompt: "What would be the result of obedience to all written in the Book of the law?",
        answer: "Prosperity and good success (Jos. 1:8)",
    },
    {
        prompt: "From what part of the body was the law not to depart?",
        answer: "The mouth (Jos. 1:8)",
    },
    {
        prompt: "Fill in the blanks:\n'Have I not commanded you? Be _____ and of good _____; do not be afraid, nor be dismayed, for the LORD your God is with you wherever you go.'",
        answer: "Strong, courage (Jos. 1:9)",
    },
    {
        prompt: "What was Joshua commanded NOT to be?",
        answer: "Afraid nor dismayed (Jos. 1:9)",
    },
    {
        prompt: "How many days were given to the people to be ready for the crossing of the Jordan?",
        answer: "Three days (Jos. 1:11)",
    },
    {
        prompt: "Which tribes were given the land on the east side of the Jordan?",
        answer: "The Reubenites, the Gadites, and half the tribe of Manasseh (Jos. 1:12)",
    },
    {
        prompt: "What besides the land had these tribes received?",
        answer: "Rest (Jos. 1:13)",
    },
    {
        prompt: "What obligation did the men of these tribes have before they could enjoy their land?",
        answer: "Help their brothers take possession of their land (Jos. 1:14-15)",
    },
    {
        prompt: "Who and what were to be left behind on the east side of the Jordan?",
        answer: "The wives, little ones, and livestock (Jos. 1:14)",
    },
    {
        prompt: "The men from these tribes told Joshua that they would fully obey him as unto whom?",
        answer: "Moses (Jos. 1:17)",
    },
    {
        prompt: "How many men did Joshua send out from Acacia Grove to spy the land, especially Jericho?",
        answer: "Two (Jos. 2:1)",
    },
    {
        prompt: "With whom did the two spies lodge?",
        answer: "Rahab (Jos. 2:1)",
    },
    {
        prompt: "Who was told that men from the children of Israel had come to Jericho to search the country?",
        answer: "The king of Jericho (Jos. 2:2)",
    },
    {
        prompt: "What was Rahab told that the men of Israel had come to do?",
        answer: "Search out all the country (Jos. 2:3)",
    },
    {
        prompt: "What did Rahab do with the two men?",
        answer: "Hid them (Jos. 2:4)",
    },
    {
        prompt: "Where did Rahab hide the two men?",
        answer: "On the roof (Jos. 2:6)",
    },
    {
        prompt: "What did Rahab use to hide the men?",
        answer: "Stalks of flax (Jos. 2:6)",
    },
    {
        prompt: "Fill in the blanks: 'and said to the men:\n\"I know that the _____ has given you the land, that the terror of you has fallen on us, and that all the inhabitants of the land are _____ because of you.\"'",
        answer: "Lord, fainthearted (Jos. 2:9)",
    },
    {
        prompt: "What had the inhabitants of Jericho heard that the Lord did to the waters of the Red Sea?",
        answer: "Dried them up (Jos. 2:10)",
    },
    {
        prompt: "What did the hearts of the people do when they heard what had happened to the waters of the Red Sea and to the Amorite kings?",
        answer: "Melted (Jos. 2:11)",
    },
    {
        prompt: "Rahab had shown kindness to the two men of Israel, and what did she ask them in return?",
        answer: "Kindness to her father’s house (Jos. 2:12)",
    },
    {
        prompt: "What did Rahab use to let the two men of Israel down through the window of her house?",
        answer: "A rope (Jos. 2:15)",
    },
    {
        prompt: "Where did Rahab instruct the two men of Israel to go?",
        answer: "The mountain (Jos. 2:16)",
    },
    {
        prompt: "How long did Rahab say the two men of Israel should hide before going on their way?",
        answer: "Three days (Jos. 2:16)",
    },
    {
        prompt: "What did the two men of Israel tell Rahab to put in the window?",
        answer: "A scarlet cord (Jos. 2:18)",
    },
    {
        prompt: "What did Rahab do as soon as she sent the two men of Israel away?",
        answer: "Bound the scarlet cord in the window (Jos. 2:21)",
    },
    {
        prompt: "Fill in the blanks: 'And they said to Joshua, \"Truly the LORD has _____ all the land into our hands, for indeed all the inhabitants of the country are _____ because of us.\"'",
        answer: "Delivered, fainthearted (Jos. 2:24)",
    },
]